吸血鬼后裔  前情提要  我建立这所学校
Previously on Legacies... You know, I opened this school
是为了保护这些孩子们的  我该如何
to protect these kids.  How am I supposed to
保护他们远离本不应该存在的东西的威胁
protect them from stuff  that's not supposed to exist?
你们都要得到同一个东西
It can't be a coincidence.
这肯定不只是个巧合
You're all coming after the same thing.
如果我把刀
If I return the knife
送回到马里之洼  我就自由了
to Malivore, I will be free.
- 马里之洼  是什么  - 是一个地狱的维度
- What's Malivore? - It's a hell dimension
会吞噬所有的生物  并且抹去他们在所有人的
that consumes creatures and wipes their existence
记忆里的存在
from the collective conscience.
有三把锁被创造出来
Three locks created
封住马里之洼
to seal Malivore shut.
三把锁都被送回去了
When all three locks return home,
马里之洼就又可以自由的张开他的死亡之颌了
Malivore is free to open its jaws of death once again.
在你们女巫团里出生的双胞胎有这样的一个命运
There's something that happens to twins born into your coven.
在你们到22岁了
When you turn 22,
双生子必须要融合
the Gemini must merge.
所以  我们两个中的一个
So, one of us is gonna
必须要杀死另一个吗
have to kill the other one?
我一直在经历着这样的记忆碎片
I keep having these flashes
就像我没办法控制我自己  然后
like I can't control myself, and...
用这个  用了这个之后  你就可以自由的进行转换
Use this. When you use it, you can turn yourself at will.
但你自己没办法转换回来
You can't turn yourself back.
所以等你准备好要转换回自己了
All you have to do is come find me when you're
你只需要找我
ready to be yourself again.
所以你是想要我相信  我的父亲
You're asking me to believe that my father
在马里之洼里面
is in Malivore.
你是他一直在尝试创造的东西
You are what he's been trying to create.
我只是需要你告诉我哪一个是真的锁
Now I need you to tell me which is the real lock,
这样我们就可以放他出来了
so we can set him free.
我们失去了他们的踪迹  但
They lost their trail, but...
但他们找到了这个
they did find this.
我知道他们要去哪儿了
I know where they're going.
让你的队伍准备好
Prep your team.
三合会最后还是绑走了兰登
Triad kidnapped Landon after all.
而霍普需要帮助  所以
And Hope needs help, so...
我得走了
I got to bounce.
在你放我出去之后吗
After you let me out of here?
那是萨尔茨曼博士的决定
That's Dr. Saltzman's call.
我希望他能尽快过来
I hope he gets here soon.
我需要回家
I need to go home.
我的家人需要我
My family needs me.
妈妈
Ma?
切断魔法了  进来吧
Power's down. Move in.
嘿  你还好吗
Hey, you okay?
我的大脑还是没有恢复
Um... my mind still won't settle down.
听着  我很抱歉  但我不能加入你们了
Look, I'm sorry, but I can't join the fight.
不用担心  我不是一个人去
Don't worry, I'm not going alone.
我的小队回应了蝙蝠侠的信号
My squad answered the Bat-Signal.
她也要来
She's coming?
我需要我所有能得到的帮助
I need all the help I can get,
所以请先把你们两个的双胞胎矛盾搁置一边
so please put your twin war on pause.
他为什么也要去
Why is he going?
他讨厌兰登  听着  你是头狼
He hates Landon. Look, you're the Alpha.
如果兰登是你的兄弟  那他也是我们的了
If Landon's your pack, that makes him ours.
- MG在哪儿  - 他在路上了
- Where's MG at?  - He's on his way.
在等他的时候我们准备一下吧  来吧
Let's load up while we wait for him. Come on.
抱歉  我们本打算敲门的
Oh, sorry. We were about to knock.
你他妈是谁
Who the hell are you?
在下是伯尔
Name's Burr.
三合会公司的
Triad Industries.
咒语
Propellere.
交给我
I got this.
你们失去了魔法
What you don't got is magic.
所以你的日光戒指不起作用了
Which is why your daylight ring won't work.
而我们有的是木桩
And what we have are stakes,
狼毒  还有其他东西
wolfsbane... and other things.
所以我觉得你们应该邀请我们进去
So I think you should invite us inside.
吸血鬼后裔
第一季   第十六集
我知道我同意重新开始做我在学校的
I know I agreed  to resume all my duties
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
全部工作  但做你的代驾司机
back at the school, but being your designated driver
可不是其中之一
was not one of them.
这次就别太计较了
Just take it easy on the turns.
我还有点醉呢
I'm still a little drunk.
那儿是发生什么了
What's going on up there?
早安  警官  这怎么堵车了呢
Morning, Officer. What's the holdup?
萨尔茨曼博士
Dr. Saltzman.
翻 译 银子小狐狸
威克里桥被封锁了
Uh, Wickery Bridge is closed.
为什么
Why?
有人把它炸了
Someone blew it up.
翻 译  文睿菌
我们在找一件叫做
We're looking for an artifact
阿里马蒂亚圣杯的圣器
known as the Chalice of Arimathea.
我们有理由相信
We have reason to believe
它是你们学校的某一件收藏品
it's part of your school's collection.
翻 译  Mónica
而你们呢要比我们更了解这个地方
Now, you know this place a lot better than we do,
所以你们能越快的帮我们找到它
so the sooner you help us find it,
翻 译  RossyGeng
我们就能越早离开
the sooner we'll be gone.
三合会感谢你们付出的时间
Triad thanks you for your time.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
翻 译  柠檬
我上司的一个仓库
A warehouse owned by my employer.
储存了他们这么多年
Stores all the supernatural objects
搜集到的超自然物品
they've confiscated over the years.
你说的是前上司吧
Think you mean former employers.
校 对   银子小狐狸
因为把我弄出来
'Cause busting me out is gonna make for
可是会让你拿到一个相当差的绩效评估
a pretty awkward performance review.
特 效   麦 斯
如果你是在担心他们有人跟踪了我们  那是不必的
If you're worried about them following us, don't be.
好吧  如果它在这儿  我们怎么能找到呢
Okay, well, if it's here, how are we gonna find it?
这地方就是个杂草堆
This place is a haystack.
好好想想吧  小弟弟
Figure it out, little brother.
你的家人还指望着你呢
Your family's counting on you.
我可以解释的
I can explain.
我们在哪儿
Where are we?
学校地下
Underneath the school.
这条隧道会带你走出大门
This tunnel is gonna lead you outside the gates.
一旦你离开了这一块区域
Your daylight ring will start to work again
你的日光戒指就会有用了
once you clear the perimeter.
我的日光戒指为什么现在没用
Why is my daylight ring not working?
你又是怎么知道的
And how do you know that it's not?
这个喷泉
This fountain.
它使学校里的魔法无效
It nullifies the magic inside the school.
我们才能不被发现的进来
That's how we got in undetected.
- 我们  - 三合会
- "We"? - Triad.
你现在和那些坏人合作了吗
You're working with the bad guys?
我们是好人
We are the good guys.
我可不这么认为
I don't see it like that.
我们之后再谈这事
We'll talk about this later.
■
看最新热播美剧
上人人视频app
可在线观看 离线缓存
各大应用市场
及AppStore皆可下载
扫描即刻下载
而现在我在努力阻止
Right now I'm trying to prevent
世界上最凶险的恶魔的觉醒
one of nature's greatest evils from rising up,
所以如果你可以离开
so if you could just go...
都不能用  我们必须要找到学校的电话
It's dead. We have to find the school cell.
找找MG的三角裤啊
Check MG's tighty-whities.
- 什么鬼  这很严肃的  - 不好意思诶
- Really? This is serious. - Oh, I'm sorry.
我们不可能都是天生就有一张面瘫的烦恼的撅着嘴的脸
We can't all be born with resting concerned pouty face.
这座书架
Didn't this shelf
之前上面不是有书的吗
used to have books on it?
是啊  这真奇怪
Yeah. That's weird.
不管他们做了什么阻断了我们这里的魔法
Whatever they're doing to block out our magic
肯定也阻断了你爸爸之前施在这里的隐藏咒语
must have knocked out a cloaking spell your dad had.
真惊讶呀  爸爸在向我们隐瞒一些东西
Big shocker. Dad's hiding something from us.
除非里面是学校的手机
Unless it has the school phone in it,
其他的都不重要
it doesn't matter.
真是抱歉  在我的全世界
Sorry I don't feel like laughing
都在崩塌的时候  我并不想笑
while my world's falling apart.
你的全世界
Your world?
那我的呢
What about my world?
我是那个最后会被
I'm the one who's eventually
我的双胞胎姊妹吸收的人
going to be absorbed by my own twin.
如果你在融合的时候输了
If you lose the Merge.
我肯定是会输的
Which I'm obviously going to.
我是脆弱的  坏掉的那一个
I'm the weak, broken one.
和以往一样  是受害者
And like clockwork-- victim.
嘿  姑娘们
Hey, guys.
找到了
Found it.
学校电话
不管是谁打来的  他都能拿到加分
Whoever this is gets extra credit.
我是霍普
It's Hope.
三合会来了
Triad's here.
大家都还好吗
Is everyone okay?
没事  但我们的能力都消失了
Yeah, but our powers are gone.
他们想要什么
What do they want?
他们说第三件圣器
They said that the third artifact
在学校的某个地方
is in the school somewhere.
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
什么什么圣杯
The Chalice of Arithmetic
之类的  我不知道  你知道什么吗
or something? I don't know. Any idea?
我们没有阿里马蒂亚圣杯的  对吧
We don't have the Chalice of Arimathea, do we?
我得查查旧军械库的记录
I'd have to check the old Armory records,
但我记得没有
but not to my knowledge.
听着  我
Uh, listen, I, uh...
我得想办法进到学校里
I've got to find my way into the school.
但你要向我保证不要做任何疯狂的事
But just promise me you're not gonna do anything crazy.
现在不只是我们有危险  兰登也有危险
We're not the only ones in danger. Landon is, too.
我不能坐以待毙啊
I can't just stand here and do nothing.
霍普  你能不能有一次
Hope, for once in your life,
听听我的话呢
will you please just listen to me?
如果三合会想要圣杯的话
If Triad wants the chalice,
那就帮他们拿到圣杯
help them get the chalice.
你现在没有了魔力
You don't have your powers.
你很脆弱  如果你继续坚持的话
You are vulnerable, and if you try to resist,
其它人会受伤的  听明白我的话了吗
someone could get hurt. Do you understand me?
明白了
Yeah.
你知道我们怎么才能进去吗
Any ideas how we're getting in?
有一个方法  但不是我们一起
Just one. But we're not.
你留在这里
You're staying here.
- 所以我们现在该怎么办呢  - 现在
- So, what do we do now?  - Now...
我们想办法找回自己的魔力
we figure out a way to get our powers back,
给这帮准军事部队的人点颜色瞧瞧
and we kick some paramilitary ass.
等等  老爸说不要做出疯狂的举动
Wait, Dad said not to do anything crazy.
我反抗你爸爸可不算疯狂的举动  这是常态
Me defying your dad isn't crazy. It's consistent.
至少我们现在知道你的立场了
Well, at least we know where you stand.
你他妈说得没错
You're damn right we do.
你好像不是很害怕我
You're not very scared of me,
是吗
are you?
那现在呢
How about now?
这就是你的计划吗
That's your plan?
- 开枪打死一个孩子  - 这把枪是绝对不会杀死
- You're gonna shoot a kid?  -  This gun would never harm
人类的小孩儿的
a human child.
但你们三个
You three, however...
这些子弹是用
These bullets were formed from
马里之洼的泥土制成的
the mud of the Malivore pit
并由三合会的科学家制作
and weaponized by Triad scientists.
他们会像小刀切过黄油一样
They can break the skin of any supernatural
穿过任何超自然生物的皮肤
like a hot knife through butter.
使皮肤溃烂  受感染
Fester. Infect them.
从内而外的分解它们
Disintegrate them from the inside out.
我们不知道圣杯在哪里
We don't know where the chalice is.
我相信你
I believe you.
但我只是想找点乐子
This is just for fun, really.
挑
Eeny...
兵
...meeny...
挑
...miney...
将
Moe.
没关系
It's okay.
没关系  没关系
It's okay. It's okay.
把他们锁起来
Lock them up.
你是不是有毛病啊
What the hell is wrong with you?
我有毛病
With me?
你刚才简直就是在求他开枪打死你
You practically begged him to shoot you.
那是因为  如果我注定要在年轻的时候死去
Because, if I'm destined to die in my prime,
我想死得光荣一点儿
it may as well be in a blaze of hero glory.
你真是太自私了
You are unbelievably selfish.
谁会自己主动挡到
Who took it upon herself to dive
我的子弹面前啊
in front of my bullet?
我还以为我们互相依赖的日子结束了呢
I thought that your codependent days were over.
这真是太令人感动了
A regrettable relapse.
喂  给我安静点儿
Hey! Keep it quiet in there.
我们又不是被关进监狱里  混蛋
We're not in the prison yard, asshat.
我真的很抱歉
You guys, I'm so sorry.
我把你们扯进了这件事里
I mean, I dragged you both into this,
而我却完全不知道该怎么逃出去
and I have absolutely no idea how to get us out of it.
这样可不大好啊  霍普
Well, that is just not good enough, Hope.
我姐姐显然就要死了  我们等了10年
My sister is clearly dying, and we did not wait ten years
才和你成为朋友  可不是为了在我们最需要你的时候
to become friends with you for you to not come through
你却没有用你那烦人的霍普·迈克尔森英雄气概
with your annoyingly perfect Hope Mikaelson heroics
来拯救我们
when we need you the most.
她说得没错  是时候改变了
She's right, for a change.
现在是你的英雄时刻  霍普
It's hero time, Hope.
我说了让你们安静些
I said keep it down in there.
有人说“英雄时刻”了吗
Did someone say "hero time"?
- 找到了  - 那咱们快离开这里吧
- I found it.  - So let's get out of here.
看来这个圣器也没那么坚不可摧  是吧
Not much of an indestructible artifact, is it?
这只是一个测试  看你是不是真的站在我这一边
This was a test to see if you were really on my side.
- 我当然不是站在你那一边  - 你确实很会撒谎
- Which I'm obviously not.   - You're a good liar,
兰登  但你也没那么擅长
Landon, but you're not great.
我知道你并没有认出圣杯
I knew you didn't recognize the chalice,
但我想看你到底能装到什么时候
but I figured it'd be fun to see how far you could take this.
既然我们都实话实说了
While we're telling the truth,
我是绝对不会帮你找这个圣器的
I'm never helping you find the artifact,
不管它到底是什么吧
whatever the hell it is.
我猜你已经帮我找到了
I'm guessing you already did.
在你拿到小刀
When you took the knife
和骨灰盒的时候  你有没有意识到
and the urn, did you even realize
你当时在做什么
what you were doing at the time,
还是说那是无意识的行为
or was it unconscious?
看看你的口袋
Check your pocket.
里面有什么
Let's find out.
糟了
Crap.
一个血液喷泉  真恶心
A blood fountain? Gross.
当面看到话更恶心  相信我
It's even grosser in person. Trust me.
我想要关掉它
I was looking for a way to shut it off,
但我一直没找到方法
but I couldn't figure out how.
好吧  我去找一下那个秘密隧道吧
All right, I'll go find the secret tunnel, I guess.
谢了  等我们恢复了魔力
Thanks. We get our magic back,
我们会占上风的
we'll have the upper hand.
这样我就能把乔西体内的污泥吸出来
And then I can siphon the sludge out of Josie,
虽然她也不会感激我
not that she'll appreciate it.
太好了  那我就只是中了一弹
Great, then I'll just be shot.
看见没  现在的你真是太刻薄了
See? The new you is so snarky.
好了  我会尽快回来的
Okay. I'm gonna be back as soon as I can.
请你看好她们俩  不要互相残杀
Please keep these two from trying to kill
也不要互相牺牲
or die for each other.
你需要去帮兰登
You need to go help Landon.
这里不需要你
We don't need you to be here.
但我不能把你们留在这里不管啊
But I can't leave you guys here.
看在弗罗多的份儿上
For the love of Frodo,
弗罗多  指环王主人公
去救你的霍比特人吧  我们能挺过去的
go rescue your Hobbit. We'll muddle through.
她又说对了  他需要你
She's right again. He needs you.
整个学年我们都在看着你
We've been watching you save the day
拯救世界  霍普
this entire school year, Hope.
现在等我们了
We got it.
- 快去拯救兰登  - 去吧
- Now go save Landon.  - Go.
如果你再在这里腻歪  我要把马里古扔出来了
If you go soft on us now, I'm just gonna hurl Maligoo.
在我们恢复魔力之前你俩这里等着
Y'all need to stay out of sight until we get the magic back
你可以和剩下的人一起歇着
and you can throw down with the rest of us.
与此同时
In the meantime,
我去召集一个军队
I'll rally up the troops.
肯定会没事的  乔
Everything's gonna be okay, Jo.
MG等等
MG, wait.
我有个想法
I have an idea.
拿上这个  你知道该怎么办
Take this. You know what to do with it.
你他妈要干嘛啊
Uh, what the hell do you think you're doing?
我要在林肯被杀时
Well, I'm taking a load off
坐的椅子上放松一下
in the chair Lincoln was killed in.
这儿的保安说他们有时候能见到他的鬼魂
The guards here say they see his ghost sometimes.
你疯了吗  我刚刚激活了一个圣器
Are you insane? I just activated the last artifact,
这意味着  就在我们说话的时候
which means that a monster is no doubt barreling
一个带着巨爪的怪物正向我们飞速爬来
its claw-footed way here as we speak.
我都要等不及了
Oh, I'm counting on it.
等它到了这里  我要把这个给它
And when it arrives, we're gonna give it this.
整个三合会都处于高度
That whole Triad facility will be
戒备的状态  所以你要么和我
on high alert, so either you and I
避过军队把这个东西扔进坑里
fight our way through an army to toss this thing
要么就让怪物替我们做
in the pit, or let the monster do it for us.
我们要找一个圣杯
We're looking for a chalice.
- 看见没  这些都是不是圣杯  - 嘿
- See, none of this is a chalice.  - Hey!
他在这儿干嘛呢
What was he doing out there?
淡定  伙计  我只是想
Chill, man. I was just
帮你们一起找这个邪恶的圣杯
looking for your unholy grail.
但你却空手而归
Except you've come back empty-handed.
去和那些人一起等着  你和他们一样都是废物
Go wait with the others. You're as useless as they are.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
不过你的身材真好啊
You're very strong, by the way.
你回来的正是时候
You got back just in time.
丑陋的三合会老大要使用金甲部队了
Ugly Triad dude's about to go Full Metal Jacket.
我知道什么东西正在扰乱我们的魔力
I know what's messing with our magic,
霍普将会关闭它
and Hope's gonna shut it down,
等她关了之后
and when that happens,
我们就能恢复魔力  那时候我们
we get our juice back, that'll be the time
- 就该行动了  - 怎么行动呢
- to make our move.  - What move, exactly?
你还记得去年你在
You remember your opening play
威克利冠军赛的开场表演吗
from the Wickery championship game last year?
- 记得啊  - 那就好
- Oh, yeah.  - All right, then.
把消息传出去
So spread the word.
听我指挥
On my signal.
好了  开始行动吧
All right, let's get it done.
你已经拿到了你想要的
You got what you wanted.
你为什么还需要我
Why do you still need me?
不是我需要你  是父亲需要你
I don't need you. Daddy does.
你才是天之骄子
You're the golden child.
他努力创造出来的儿子  记得吗
The one he was trying to create, remember?
完美的儿子
The perfect son.
能创造新血统的人
The one who could create the new bloodline.
因为你  他才能够延续这个物种
Because of you, he'll be able to launch the species.
我才17岁
I'm 17.
我对这什么鬼的
I'm not interested in, like,
繁衍物种的事情不感兴趣
procreating or whatever, okay?
更何况这意味着繁衍出
Especially if it means I'm spawning
一批邪恶大军
an army of evil minions.
我之前没提过吗
Oh, didn't I mention?
你只是宿主
You're just the host.
什么
The what?
从生物学角度来说  你只是宿主
The host. Biologically speaking,
- 作为活体  - 我知道宿主是什么
you're the living organism... I know what a host is!
我看过  人体异形  这电影
I've seen Invasion  of the Body Snatchers.
你开玩笑呢吧  告诉我
Are you kidding me? Tell me you're
这只是个兄弟间的蹩脚玩笑
pulling some kind of lame brotherly prank right now.
你不是不甘于平凡嘛
You wanted to be special, right?
希望自己能有一个家
The foster kid looking for a family,
坚信自己身负使命  希望自己能找到
believing that you had a purpose if only you could find it.
事实证明你的使命
Turns out your purpose
就是做史上最强大怪物的
is to be a meat suit for the most powerful monster
肉身而已
ever to walk the earth.
这样说起来的确很惨
Well, probably sounds worse than it is.
一定是我们的新朋友来了
That must be our new friend.
你觉得会是什么  半人马还是飞马
What do you think it'll be? Centaur? Pegasus?
妙极了
Even better.
都交给你了  做你该做的吧
It's all yours. Just do your thing.
太蠢了  弟弟
Dick move, brother.
我猜  你没有带说明书来吧
I don't suppose you come with an instruction manual.
- 我叫你等我的  - 发生了
I told you to wait for me. In a shocking
太多事  我忘了要等你
turn of events, I ignored you.
- 霍普  说起这个  - 别长篇大论了
Yeah, Hope, about that... Save the speech.
好吗  我已经遭报应了
Okay? I've paid the price.
我知道  你的手臂怎么了
I see that. What happened to your arm?
三合会的人用马里之洼的泥攻击我
That Triad guy shot at us with Malivore mud.
他肯定也打中了我
He must have gotten me, too.
我都没感觉到
I-I didn't even feel it.
因为这玩意伤不了我
Because it doesn't affect me.
等等  还有谁被击中了吗
Wait, who else got shot?
萨尔茨曼博士  你必须相信我
Dr. Saltzman, you have to trust me.
- 乔茜会没事  - 乔茜被击中了吗
Josie's gonna be just... Josie got shot?
是的  但MG和丽兹已经在想办法了
Yes, but MG and Lizzie are on it,
他们一定能治好她的
and I think that they can fix everything.
如果我能想个办法把这玩意关掉
If I can just figure out a way to turn this stupid thing off,
那他们就能恢复法力了
then they can get their magic back.
很显然  关掉这个其实超简单
Which is super easy, apparently.
你怎么知道该这么关的
How did you know how to do that?
这是一件
This is a dark object,
由一群已经灭绝的女巫般的人创造的
created by a group of extinct witch-like people
名为游者的黑暗之物
called the Travelers.
他们的专长是反魔法
Anti-magic was kind of their thing.
三合会他们是怎么进来的
How did Triad even get it in here?
他们怎么知道这里有隧道
How did they know that there were tunnels?
这些事情我待会会和你解释的
Listen, I will explain everything to you later, okay?
但现在  我得去找乔茜
But right now, I have to get to Josie.
等等
Wait.
给她一小瓶我的血
Give her a vial of my blood.
治疗狼人咬伤的那个
From the werewolf bite cures.
为什么
Why?
我也等会再解释
I'll explain later, too.
没有用
It's not working.
为什么会没效果
Why isn't it working?
也许这毒吸不出来
Maybe it can't be siphoned.
那这样你会死的
But then you'll die.
这样我们俩就可以不融合了
That's one way for you to avoid the Merge.
- 作弊  - 不
Cheater. No.
我不准你做烈士
Uh-uh. You do not get to be the martyr.
该死的应该是我
That was my job.
做烈士我也比你更厉害
I'm obviously better at that, too.
不应该是这样的
It wasn't supposed to be like this.
我才是那个身心破碎的
I'm the broken one.
想想你参加我葬礼时会穿得多美吧
Just think of the amazing outfit that you'll wear to my funeral.
抱歉我不是个好姐姐
I'm sorry I was so awful.
我更抱歉
I'm sorrier.
别再跟我比了
Stop competing with me.
帮我一把
And help me up.
MG需要我们  荣耀之光永远闪耀
MG needs us. Blaze of glory, right?
你确定你能行吗
You sure you're up for this?
一点也不确定
Not at all.
但要是你奋起战斗  那我也要放手一搏
But if you're fighting, I'm fighting, too.
那个吊坠是干嘛用的
What's the bling for?
这能帮我听到细微的声音
Making quiet things heard.
塞尔瓦托公马队  冲啊
Salvatore Stallions! Let's ride!
佩德罗  快传
Pedro, now.
杰德
Jed.
杰德  传给我
Jed, I'm open!
* I'm invincible... *
凯勒布  带孩子们上校车
Kaleb, get the kids to the bus.
女巫们
Witches...
让他们尝尝我们的厉害
...make it rain.
她们的法力恢复了
Their magic's back.
来人  去隧道搞定这事
Somebody get to the tunnels and fix this!
别动
Don't move.
小兄弟  干得漂亮
Nice job, little man.
来  抱紧我
Come here. Hold on tight.
所以你以为自己是超级英雄什么的吗
So you think you're a superhero or something?
■
看最新热播美剧
上人人视频app
可在线观看 离线缓存
各大应用市场
及AppStore皆可下载
扫描即刻下载
说实话  是有点
Honestly? Kind of.
可惜我带了克你的武器
Too bad I got Kryptonite.
可惜我的朋友超级厉害
Too bad I got Super Friends.
乔  坐好
Here Jo, sit
好吧  乔
All right, Jo,
你脸色很不好
you don't look too hot.
我们得把布尔抓来
We got to go after Burr.
别担心
Don't worry.
我也有霍普的魔法吊坠
I got magical Hope bling, too.
如果乔西和丽齐能帮我施隐身魔法
If Josie and Lizzie can help me with a veiling spell...
他就看不到我来抓他了
...he'll never see me coming.
快上  上去
Right up, up there.
好的
All right.
大家都没事吧
You guys okay?
好啦可以了
All right, all right, all right.
来
All right.
小伙计  坐这儿
Here you go, little man.
坐好  好吗
Sit tight, okay?
看看四周
Look around, man.
你要的破圣杯不在这  好吗
Your stupid cup ain't here, okay?
你输了
You lost.
不  看看你还能失去多少吧
No. Look how much you can still lose.
拜托  大哥  我女儿受伤了
Come on, man, please. My daughter's injured.
她需要我  放我去找她吧
She needs me. Just let me get to her.
转过身去
Turn around.
- 太好了  又来人了  - 手放身后
Great. Now it's a party. Hands behind your back.
好了  下手轻点
Okay. Take it easy.
太好了  我铁定要给你加薪了
Yes! You're definitely getting a raise.
看牙能报销吗
With dental.
嘿
Hey.
听我说  别
Listen to me, don't...
你不会下手伤害孩子的
You don't want to do this, okay?
把枪口转向我
Point the gun at me.
什么鬼
What the hell?
拉斐  这里交给我
I got it from here, Raf.
到树林里去等霍普回来
Hit the woods until Hope comes back.
你和他们一样  都是怪物
You're a monster, just like him,
我要把你们一网打尽
and you all need to be put down.
我宁愿做个怪物
Rather be a monster
也不会做石像的
than a paperweight.
我以为你早就走了
I thought you were long gone.
约翰·斯图尔特会弃团队于不顾吗
Would John Stewart leave the Corps hanging?
约翰·斯图尔特：绿灯军团的正式成员
当然不会
Hell no.
因为他是绿灯军团里最厉害的  你也明白
'Cause he's the best Green Lantern, and you know it.
帅哥  要保持联系
Stay in touch, cutie.
好的
Okay.
老爸  情况太糟了
Daddy, this is so bad.
乔茜
Josie...
乔茜  乔茜  快把这个喝了
Josie, Josie, drink this now.
他们说革命是混乱肮脏的
They say revolution is messy.
我不在乎
And I'm okay with that.
你没必要这么做  一切都结束了
You don't need to do that. It's over.
要是我们不这样警告三合会
If we don't use him to send Triad a message,
谁能保证他们下次不会派更坏的人来呢
who's to say they won't send someone worse next time?
这些三合会的人只是胆小的恶霸
These Triad guys are just scared bullies,
只是因为他们觉得自己失去了对一些没有能力
lashing out because they think they're losing control
他们本就没能力掌控的东西的控制  所以才来伤害我们的
over something they had no power over in the first place.
你曾经跟我说过
Like you told me once,
我们更敏捷  更强大  更优秀
we're faster, we're stronger, we're better.
实际上  他们知道
Deep down, they know that.
所以坚强点
So just be better.
我们不需要靠杀了他们才能证明
We don't need to prove it by killing them.
看看你
Look at you, man.
长成大人了
Baby's all grown up.
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
我们被误导了
We were misled.
圣器并不在这
The artifact was never here.
伯尓  他  做的太过了
And Burr, he... he took it too far.
用枪指着孩子们
Pointing guns at children.
他不会再做这份工作了
He'll never work in the field again.
如果这是道歉的话  那太差劲了
If that's supposed to be an apology, it sucks.
你怎么能和那样的人共事
How could you work with guys like that?
三合会是我爸的遗产
Triad is my father's legacy.
也是我爷爷的遗产
And his father before him.
也是你的  直到
And it was meant to be yours, too, until...
直到我成了你们憎恨的怪物
Until I became one of the monsters you guys hate.
三合会在世上一直在做伟大的事
Triad has been doing great work in the world.
如果这是咱家遗产的话
If this is our family's legacy...
那我们就做不成家人了
...we cannot be family anymore.
听我说
Look, hear me out.
你能听到是吧
You can hear, right?
面对面  如果你是
Uh, man-to-man, if you ever were one...
你被利用了
You're being used.
我知道那种感觉  所以咱
And-and I know what that feels like, so let's...
你没有眼睛怎么还能打中我
Ow! Ow, how do you even do that without your seeing-eye horse?
你是靠情感支持的吗
Or is it more of an emotional support horse?
不不不  求你  求你别扔进去
Oh, no, no, no. Please, please, please, don't!
霍普
Hope.
我就知道你能找到我
I knew you'd find me.
我按照你留言的线索找了
I just followed the clues you left in that voice mail.
你真是解谜高手  我们应该
You're great at riddles. We should probably
给你的课程里加入打斗
add fight training to your coursework, though.
是啊
Yeah.
欢迎做笔记
Feel free to take notes.
我好奇霍普要干嘛
I wonder what Hope's up to.
我打赌她已经救了兰登和世界了
I bet she saved Landon already, and the world.
她擅长这样
Yeah, she's pretty good at that.
希望  她可以马上就回来了
Hopefully she gets back soon.
否则  拉夫就住在狗窝里了
Otherwise, Raf's gonna end up in the doghouse.
真的狗窝
Literally.
说到这  别告诉爸爸  要不然我们也要住狗窝了
Speaking of, don't tell Dad, unless we'll end up there, too.
你从他办公室拿的  为什么
You took that thing from his office? Why?
我不想在闹别扭的时候告诉你
I didn't want to tell you when we were fighting,
但是我破开了锁  在我做的
but I busted the lock, and I recognized this
所有融合的研究中认出了这个
from all the Merge research I've been doing.
怎么看起来眼熟呢
Why does that look familiar?
不知道
I don't know.
但我也对它有印象
But I remember it somehow, too.
姑娘们  有件事我想和你俩谈谈
Girls, there's something I need to talk to you both about.
我辜负了你们
I failed you.
我建校的目的
You see, my purpose in founding this school
就是为我女儿及同样的自然生物们
was to create a safe space for my daughters
提供安全的住所
and for supernaturals like them.
但今天  我却没实现这个目标
But today, I fell short of that goal,
你们超乎了
while all of you exceeded
我所有的预期
every expectation I had ever set for you.
因为今天  你们面对了
Because today, you were confronted
迄今最可怕的怪物
by the worst monster you've faced yet:
无知的人类
ignorant human beings.
悲哀的是
Sadly,
我也是其中之一
I am one of them.
那些三合会渗透到学校  威胁你们性命的
The plans and methods that Triad used to infiltrate our school
那些计划方法都是我想出的
and endanger your lives were mine.
是我多年间偶然间想出的
A contingency plan that I had developed
分享给关心学生的父母的计划
and shared with concerned parents over the years,
也包括维罗尼亚·格蕾丝莉
including Veronica Greasley.
但是
But...
没有我的计划她就不可能背叛
her betrayal would not have been possible without mine.
是这样  她用来
You see, the dark object
剥夺你们独特能力的黑暗物品
that she used to disarm your unique abilities
就是一手放到了
was put in place by me,
只有我自己知道的地道里的
in the secret tunnel that only I had known about,
因为我想  也许有一天
because I thought that, perhaps one day,
这个世界需要被保护免受你们的能力的伤害
it was the world that would need to be protected from your gifts,
而不是需要你们的能力
rather than the other way around.
我能弥补失信的唯一方法
The only way I can atone for this breach of trust
就是交由你们决定
is to leave it up to you to decide
是否还让我做你们的校长
whether I should remain as your headmaster.
我会召集荣誉委员会投票
The honor council will convene, they will vote,
我将尊重他们的一切决定
and I will respect whatever decision that they make.
无论结果如何
Whichever way this goes,
我都想感谢你们
I want to thank you,
所有人
all of you,
让我明白了  我女儿将生活的世界
for making me understand that the world my daughters inherit
将会变得更好
will be in better hands.
咒语
Incendia!
他死不了的  你了解科幻的
He won't die. You know sci-fi stuff.
帮我  我该怎么杀了他
Help me. How do I kill him?
无头马人很奇幻
Uh, Headless Horseman is more fantasy.
说重点
Get to the helpful part.
在蒂姆·伯顿的电影里
In the Tim Burton movie,
他们给他娶了新娘才打败他的
they defeated him by giving him a bride.
这不是我的最佳选项
That wouldn't be my first choice.
我也是
Me, neither.
在卡通片里  他长着南瓜头
In-in the O.G. cartoon, he had a pumpkin head.
他可能把它和他的马放在一起了
That... he might keep it with his horse?
不对  他的甲胄下面一定有头
Correction! He's got it under his cape.
杀了头  身体就死了  这就是科幻
Kill the head, the body dies. That's science faction.
很好
Great.
一个头出来了
One head coming up.
为什么潮乎乎的
Oh, God, why is it moist?
给我  给我
Uh, give me, give me.
死去吧  蒂姆·伯顿
Suck on that, Tim Burton.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
好吧
Um, okay, um...
我准备了这段演讲
So I had this entire speech that I practiced
- 是对着你的棱晶幻象练的  - 我的什么
- with your prismatic hologram. - My what?
但我知道你唯一想知道的是真相
But I know that the only thing you want from me is the truth.
真相就是
And the truth is...
我爱你
...I love you.
很抱歉我隐藏了
I'm really sorry about all the secrets
那么多秘密  但是我
that I've kept, but I'm...
我最抱歉的就是隐藏了这个
I'm mostly sorry about keeping that one.
我爱你  兰登·卡比
'Cause I love you, Landon Kirby.
这不算什么秘密
I mean, it wasn't a huge secret,
因为我也爱你  霍普·迈克尔森
because I love you, too, Hope Mikaelson.
你做了什么我都原谅你
And I forgive you for anything that needs it.
我知道你到这里是我看着要输了
And I know it looked like I was losing when you got here,
但是凤凰就是这样战斗的  所以
but that's just how Phoenix combat looks, so...
没什么能比得上年轻的爱
Nothing like young love, is there?
遗憾的是它稍纵即逝
Shame it has to be so short-lived.
你会发现的  弟弟
You'll find, baby brother,
我们家族最糟糕的品质就是
one of our family's worst traits is...
我们都笨手笨脚
...well, we're terribly clumsy.
不
No!
你们不鼓个掌吗
Aren't you gonna clap or something?
这真是个强大的举动
That was a total power move.
- 该死  凤凰的战斗不开玩笑的  - 我们得想想
- Damn. Phoenix combat's no joke. - Okay. We got to think.
我们得想个办法不让他觉醒
We got to figure something out to keep him from rising.
你说的他是什么意思
What do you mean, "him"?
我们有好多话要说清
Ooh, we have a lot to catch up on.
这个注意真的是太奇怪了  乔茜  霍普现在失踪了
This whole idea is wack, Josie. Hope's M.I.A.
在她回来之前拉夫都变不回人
Raf is stuck being a werewolf until she gets back.
蒂格小姐都不在学校工作了
Ms. Tig don't even work at the damn school anymore.
我们的投票关乎你父亲的未来
Hey, look, we're voting on the fate of my father.
- 你认为我什么感觉  - 听好
- How do you think I feel? - Look,
我只是想召集委员会
I just want to convene the council.
好吗
Okay?
觉得咱们都有很多话要说
I figure we both got a lot to say.
但我们需要多数选票
But we need a majority vote.
霍普很快就回来了
Hope is coming back soon.
和兰登一起
With Landon.
她也会把拉夫带回来
And then she's going to bring Raf back, too.
还真是复杂啊
Wow. That's a lot to take in.
- 马里之洼是你爸  - 很奇怪吧
- So Malivore's your dad? Weird, huh?
他杀不死  所以三合会才把他变成泥了
And he can't be killed, which is why Triad turned him to goo?
你学的真快
You're a quick study.
但没有什么是永生的  我是说  不会真的永生
But nothing's ever immortal. I mean, not really.
自然不会允许的  总会有一些漏洞
Nature won't allow it. There's always a loophole.
有什么好点子吗
Any brilliant ideas?
因为我觉得快没有时间了
Because I think we're running out of time.
就一个
Just one.
但你不会喜欢的
But you're gonna hate it.
吻我
Kiss me.
我一点都不讨厌
I didn't hate that at all.
不是那个
Not that.
这个
This.
霍普  你找到兰登了吗
Hope. Did you find Landon?
嗯
Yeah.
那告诉我你在哪儿
Okay, well, tell me where you are.
乔治亚州  堡谷
Fort Valley, Georgia.
等我解决完的时候兰登需要你  你得记下来
Landon's gonna need you when I'm done. You have to write it down.
- 慢着  你在三合会总部吗  - 是
- Wait. You're at Triad Headquarters?  - Yeah.
不过别担心  这里的人都死了
Uh, don't worry, though. Everyone here is dead.
听着  你说的东西都毫无道理
Okay, listen, you're not making any sense.
让兰登接电话好吗
Just put Landon on the phone.
不行  他试着阻止我
I can't. Uh, he would have tried
那我不得不把他杀了
to stop me, so I had to kill him, too.
啥
What?
他会回来的  别担心
He'll come back. Don't worry.
就算我回不来也别担心
Even if I don't.
霍普
Hope,
你做事前
tell me what the hell you're about
能不能告诉我你要做什么
to do right now before you do it.
克拉克赢了  他找到了最后一件圣器
Clarke won. He found the final artifact,
他把它丢进了坑里  哦对了
and he tossed it into the pit, which is Landon's father,
那是兰登的爸爸
by the way.
马里之洼马上就要崛起了 除非我能先阻止他
And now Malivore's gonna rise unless I stop him.
怎么阻止
Stop him how?
兰登那里有所有的答案  但是
Landon got all the answers, but,
简单点说  马里之洼是用狼人  吸血鬼  还有女巫的血
basically, Malivore was created by the blood of a werewolf,
血组成的
a witch and a vampire.
本来创造他的人可以毁灭他
It used to be that only they could destroy what they created,
但是大自然找到了漏洞
but nature found a loophole.
大自然造出了我
By making me.
三重混血  我就是那个漏洞  霍普  你听我说
The Tribrid. I'm the loophole. Hope, you listen to me.
这只是个理论  你都不知道
Now, this is a theory, okay, and you don't even know
这会不会成功  所以你先别动
if this is gonna work, so you just sit tight,
你等我到那里再说
and you wait for me to get there.
没时间了
There's no time.
我一直以为我是宇宙的错误
I've always thought that I was a cosmic mistake,
一个本不该出生的人
someone who should never have been born.
但是经过这些我明白了  我的任务很明晰了
But after all this time, I mean, my purpose is finally clear.
想想吧
Think about it.
我就是这一切的答案
I'm the answer to all of this.
我能记住关于马里之洼的事  别人都不知道
I can remember things about Malivore that no one else can.
三合会的武器影响不到我
That Triad weapon didn't affect me.
我的血治好乔西了吗
Did my blood heal Josie?
我不接受这一切
I am not okay with this.
我明白
I know.
但是你会接受的  因为一旦我跳进那里
But you will be, because once I toss myself into that pit,
学校里的所有人都不会记得我
no one at school will remember me.
包括你
Including you.
霍普 你听我说
Hope. You listen to me.
多年来我一直折磨自己
I've spent years torturing myself,
问我自己为什么我的父亲为了我牺牲了自己
asking myself why my father sacrificed himself for me,
但是现在
to get to this point where,
我明白了
I mean, I totally understand it.
但我不想让你再经受
And I don't want you to have to
那种痛苦  萨尔茨曼博士
go through that pain, Dr. Saltzman.
你已经经历得够多了
You've been through enough.
我不想让学校里的人想念我
And I don't want anyone at school to miss me,
因为他们是我的朋友
because they're my friends.
要不是我自己一直折磨自己
Maybe I would have seen that sooner
我说不定会早点明白
if I hadn't been beating myself up all this time.
这时候你就该告诉我
This is where you tell me
即使你希望我不这么做
that even though you wish you could
你也会理解我是在做对的事
change my mind, you know I'm doing the right thing.
这时候你就该告诉我你为我而骄傲了
This is the part where you tell me you're proud of me.
你知道的  我为你而骄傲
You know I'm proud of you.
你知道的
You know it.
你需要我做什么
What is it you need me to do?
叫后勤来
Call maintenance.
让他们收拾我的房间
Have 'em pack up my room.
拿走我的档案
Take my files,
还有所有你一直记录的关于我的东西
all those notes I know that you keep about me,
然后烧了他们
and burn them.
把兰登的日志也一起烧了
Along with Landon's journal.
听着  要是你想抹去你自己
Listen, if you want to erase yourself,
那取决于你  但是你不能要求我也这么做
that is on you, okay, but you can't ask me to do it, too.
我很抱歉  萨尔茨曼博士
I'm sorry, Dr. Saltzman.
但是所有人里我最相信你
But I trust you more than I trust anyone.
我也希望我能早点搞清楚这些
I wish I would have figured that out sooner, too.
我得挂了
I got to go.
霍普
Hope,
听我说  等等
listen to me. Wait.
不可以
Not an option. Uh-uh.
向我保证  你会按我说的做
Uh, promise me you're gonna do what I said.
向我保证
Promise me.
好吧
All right. Fine.
我保证
I promise.
抱歉
Ooh. Sorry.
我不小心听到了
I was eavesdropping.
你在等什么
What are you waiting for?
我猜你会阻止我
I assumed you were gonna try to stop me.
哦不
Hell no.
我只是想复活我的父亲
I was only trying to raise my father
因为我怕他
because I'm terrified of him,
而且我知道总有一天  他会跑出来的
and I knew he'd find a way out someday.
但是要是关于漏洞那事你是对的话
But if you're right about this loophole-- can actually
那样可以直接把这东西永久干掉
kill the bastard once and for all--
请自便
be my guest.
要是你错了
And if you're wrong,
反正你死了  也没有什么损失
well, no harm done because you'll be dead.
所以去吧
So go on.
我会支持你
I'll be rooting for you.
但你不会止步于此
That's not all you'll be doing.
咒语
Imitantor Pupulus.
你刚刚这一句
Whatever you think you just did
没用啊
didn't work.
你怎么做到的
How'd you do that?
我怎么了
Why did I do that?
基础模仿咒
It's a basic mimic spell.
二年级的时候学的
We learned it in second grade.
还有  二年级的时候
Also in second grade...
跟着领路人走
Follow the Leader.
- 你不必这样的  - 我知道
You don't have to do this. I know.
但是这是我唯一在享受的部分
But it's the only part I'm actually enjoying.
很遗憾 你手脚不协调
Too bad you're so clumsy.
你没事吧
You okay?
是
Yeah.
我不知道怎么了
I don't know what came over me.
* There's danger... *
是啊
Yeah. Um....
我们为什么有五票
Why do we have five voting tiles?
你  我
You, me,
学校监护人  拉斐尔
school guardian, Rafael.
才四个啊
That's four.
* It's coming *
我也不明白
Beats me.
* There's no escape *
* Oh *
* Oh-oh, oh-oh *
堡谷  去找兰登
* Oh *
* Oh-oh, oh-oh *
* Oh, oh *
* Oh *
* Oh-oh, oh-oh *
* Oh, oh... *
萨尔茨曼博士
Dr. Saltzman?
兰登
Landon.
我来了
I'm on my way.
好了
Okay. Uh...
我真不知道发生了什么
I don't... I don't really know what happened.
我也不知道
Yeah, well, that makes two of us.
我刚刚发现一张纸条  说你需要我
I just found a note that you'd need me.
我想我确实需要
I guess I do.
* Who will rise? *
* Who will answer the call? *
谁留的字条啊
Who left it?
我也不知道
I have no idea.
* This is savage *
我尽快过来
I'll be there as soon as I can.
* This is primal. *
■
人人视频APP
在线观看美剧
离线高清缓存
更有海量高清电影
扫码即刻下载
特别推荐
■
各大应用市场均可下载
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）